# **Sonny Kinchlea**

### **PERSONAL DETAILS**

Gants Hill Essex United Kingdom

Mobile: 07506571078 E-mail: sonnykinchlea@hotmail.co.uk

# PERSONAL PROFILE

I am a programmer with an ambition to have a career in web/software development. I work well under pressure but also take my time to learn new skills and produce the best quality results.

Over the past year I have been developing my skills as a junior programmer and developing using a range of frontend and backend languages.

My years of experience working in various customer-facing and most recently a junior programming position have helped me gain valuable skills in teamwork, individual initiative and communication.

#### **EDUCATION**

Sept 2015 - July 2018	University of Greenwich					Greenwich
BSc 2:1 - Game Design & Development						
Sept 2011 - July 2013	Epping Forest College					Epping
BTEC Level 3 Diploma Create Media						
Sept 06 - June 2011	Oaks Park High School					Gants Hill
	GCSE	English Language	С	Creative Media	В	
		Mathematics	С	History	С	
		Science	С	ICT	В	

#### **WORK EXPERIENCE**

## **REAPSOURCE**

July 2019 - April 2020

#### **Junior Software Developer**

As one of only 2 developers, my role at ReapSource was to design and develop a team-collaboration website/application that included file management, goal tracking and instant messaging features.

- · Review and amend initial website designs using Adobe XD.
- Discuss and plan additional new features and the timeframe they could be developed in.
- · Hold Scrum meetings bi-weekly and review what went well and what could have gone better.
- · Design and develop the frontend of the application using JavaScript, HTML, CSS and jQuery.
- Develop the logic for the backend of the application using C# asp.NET and Ajax to pass data to the frontend.

# **SKY STUDIOS**

July 2017 - September 2019

## **Event Host**

Sky Studios at the O2 Arena is a promotional and hospitality area where customers can interact with Sky branded games and entertainment. On show nights, guests can be admitted to the backstage bar and dining area.

- Inspect and collect tickets to the bar and dining lounge.
- Walk visitors through the entertainment experiences
- Engage with visitors and discuss Sky offerings.
- Interact with spectators and inform them of information they need about the Arena.

# **WORK EXPERIENCE**

#### **TESCO**

April 2012 - January 2017

#### **Customer Assistant**

Working on both customer-facing and warehouse roles. Nights, days and everything in-between.

- Greeting customers from a wide range of different backgrounds and cultures;
- · Responsible for managing stock levels and maintaining appearance and cleanliness of the store front;
- · A willingness to help clients with a variety of queries in a busy working environment;
- Worked in a diverse team under pressure, developing excellent communication skills whilst maintaining high levels of service even during busy hours;
- Developed excellent problem-solving skills when dealing with customer requests;
- · Handling money and clearing tills;
- Customer Service.
- · Assisting in training new staff and assisting in opening and closing the store.

# **SKILLS**

- HTML, CSS, JavaScript & jQuery
- asp.NET
- PHP
- Bootstrap
- Integrating API's
- · Unity Game Engine

## **INTERESTS**

- Reading
- Cycling
- Travelling
- Programming

REFERENCES AVAILABLE ON REQUEST, THANK YOU FOR READING MY CV.